TAYDEN FLITCROFT

🗣 Texas, United States 🛎 taydengoodeill@gmail.com 🛘 (503) 569-7894 🛅 https://www.linkedin.com/in/tayden-flitcroft-225013147/

http://profile.taydenflitcroft.com

SUMMARY

A natural leader who enjoys leading by example in a team environment while also demonstrating success in individual tasks; dedicated, dependable, and experienced with effective problem-solving and communication skills. Over 2 years of computer diagnosis and repair on Windows and macOS based computers with expertise with network, hardware and software troubleshooting and repair.

EXPERIENCE

Advanced Repair Agent

Geek Squad

December 2018 - Present, San Antonio, TX

- $\cdot \ Diagnose \ and \ repair \ per sonal \ computer \ issues, achieving \ an \ average \ repair \ rate \ of \ over 1 \ repair \ per \ hour \ with \ less \ than \ a \ 1\% \ return \ for \ redo \ rate.$
- · Provide recommendations to extend usability and reliability of customer computer.
- Train and develop new technicians beginning their IT careers.
- · Collaborated with Google for a stretch assignment to offer Geek Squad services combined with Google's Nest products to realtors from January 2019 July 2019.

Microsoft Expert

Best Buy

October 2018 - December 2018, Dallas, TX

- $\cdot \, \text{Demonstrate, discuss, and sell Microsoft products and services.} \\$
- · Maintained Top 5 in sales and experience month to month with over 100 other Microsoft Experts in my area.
- · Train and develop peers regarding Microsoft's latest offerings for products and services.
- · Operate directly with Microsoft to provide updates to the business's successes and failures within Best Buy, as well as provide recommendations to improve to current operating model.

Apple Master

Best Buy

January 2018 - October 2018, Dallas, TX

- · Manage sales metrics for Apple products.
- · Train peers on good sales practices to display the Apple ecosystem that their products utilize.
- · Collaborate with management and Apple Sales Specialists to ensure all customer needs remain fulfilled by ensuring a full purchasing solution for all customers is offered.
- Ensure all customers received the best shopping experience possible by providing world-class customer service.

Supervisor

Starbucks

October 2015 - October 2017, Prosper, TX

- $\cdot \ Manage\ daily\ store\ operations\ including\ inventory\ and\ cash\ management\ while\ ensuring\ standard\ operating\ procedures\ are\ maintained\ by\ employees.$
- Train new employees on processes and procedures for their individual roles.
- $\cdot \ \ \text{Develop existing baristas to assist them with their transition into a leadership role.}$
- $\cdot \, \text{Maintain customer experience during all hours of business to ensure a sensational visit to the store.} \\$

EDUCATION

Certification in Audio Engineering

Collin County Community College • Frisco, TX • 2018 • 3.0

Apple iOS Certified Technician

2019

SKILLS

Peer Training and Development | Computer Hardware Repair | macOS and Windows Operating System Repair | Network Configuration and Management